{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "________ of these two paths is the shortest?",
      "a": "Whose",
      "b": "What",
      "c": "Whom",
      "d": "Which",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who ________ at the meeting?",
      "a": "did speak",
      "b": "did spoke",
      "c": "spoke",
      "d": "does spoke",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Who: used to ask or talk about which person is involved, or what the name of a person is\n+ Ask for Subject: Who + Verb",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "________ hand do you use for writing?",
      "a": "Whom",
      "b": "Which",
      "c": "Whose",
      "d": "Who",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Which: used for asking for a specific choice from a limited number of possibilititesÂ ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do they know what ________ the fire?",
      "a": "caused",
      "b": "did cause",
      "c": "did caused",
      "d": "does cause",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- What + V + O: used as the object of a verb (know)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who ________ with you?",
      "a": "did came",
      "b": "did come",
      "c": "come",
      "d": "came",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Who: used to ask or talk about which person is involved, or what the name of a person is\n+ Ask for Subject: Who + Verb",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who _______ the bill last night?",
      "a": "paid",
      "b": "did pay",
      "c": "did it pay",
      "d": "pay",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Who: used to ask or talk about which person is involved, or what the name of a person is ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you see that man?' ' ________ one?'",
      "a": "Whose",
      "b": "Who",
      "c": "Which",
      "d": "Whom",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "________ did you go to the theatre with?",
      "a": "With who",
      "b": "With which",
      "c": "Who with",
      "d": "Whom",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Whom: We use whom to ask which person receives an action",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who ________ that short story?",
      "a": "writes",
      "b": "wrote",
      "c": "did write",
      "d": "did wrote",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Who: used to ask or talk about which person is involved, or what the name of a person is\n+ Ask for Subject: Who + Verb",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can you tell me what _______ the accident?",
      "a": "did cause",
      "b": "caused",
      "c": "did it cause",
      "d": "cause",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- To tell somebody something (What + V + O)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}